{
    "id": "bd310480251d4e97bf6e42d51007b4b3",
    "title": "Prepositions And Conjunctions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8355fcf5f90d48f982178fdcceea8e4d",
            "title": "Prepositions And Conjunctions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t eaten anything ………………………….. morning.",
                    "description": "Since indicates the starting point. It is common with perfect tenses.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… it was a public holiday, I decided to visit my parents.",
                    "description": "Both as and since can show the reason. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Since",
                        "As",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He missed the bus ……………………………. he was late.",
                    "description": "Because shows reason.",
                    "answers": [
                        "because",
                        "so",
                        "therefore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It has been ages …………………………….. I heard anything from her.",
                    "description": "Since indicates the starting point. It is common with perfect tenses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "as",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The evening was …………………………… hot that I started sweating profusely.",
                    "description": "Note the pattern 'so...that'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was ……………………………….. busy that he could not attend the party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher scolded the boys …………………………… they hadn’t done their homework.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "because",
                        "so",
                        "though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the office ………………………………. I used to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "where",
                        "there"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. it was a hot night, I slept in the patio",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Thus",
                        "Even as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should see a doctor ……………………………. you are not feeling well.",
                    "description": "If expresses a condition. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "even if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. she hasn’t arrived yet, we will have to go without her.",
                    "description": "As shows the reason.",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "So",
                        "Hence"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………………. it is raining, you cannot go now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "Thus",
                        "Even as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}